Hello, welcome to the tree episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today we are the
last one. Second reader, if you like
this one, but before going there,
you all must have seen the first lesson
and must have written at least 40-50 sentences from it.
Making wickets is very
important. Now you should know the deficit
rotor ball or this news flying ball or
duty. So if you have done it
perfectly, if you have made 50 sentences, then the
rest is very easy. Look,
if you have not done it yet and if
you are watching this, then you will have a little
problem. Then you will get confused with the three tables.
And its reverse is also
that if you are done then you have done almost 20%. The
rest of the things that you are going to learn today,
we are going to use them sometimes, I am going to
give its treatment in the back side,
please make sure that if you are starting here, then
everything is clear to you before that. Okay, so let's start.
First of all, let's start with a little division.
Okay, so  First of all, what is
Aditya added to deliver June, what does it mean,
because of which there will be no change, there will be an attractive
change, okay, just like we used to do it in Hindi,
we will do the same here too, so you know what,
unfortunately, there will be not one but
three tables, what types will there be,
you saw the first one is with a different article, with
milk in English, the second one is
with indefinite article, which is
how it is in English, and the third one is without
article, and the third one was the last one, we had
learnt it perfectly,
we had learnt it the whole time, we had learnt how to do bread oil or
bread phone, so when the
screen settings show the
table,
my tab in the genitive said that we are going to
see whether this much or not, as we
said that normal, your stomach pain, step leaf,
how did we do this year, let me just
solve the mail and show you, in the red ball rank
wonderland, in the nominative, this dust rotor
ball has come, that dough bread has been underlined,
puja tubewell, this news hotel ball and you can
withdraw the red corner line, dot email, this
kilometer and the table is very simple but  If
this is clear then the next is very simple so let's
see the second part, with these different
parties, that is in English and
with eyeliner, so let's take an example,
so we can say that this red
ball or if it is medical, then let's
see how to do it, if it is suitable for that, then
if you see this table,
like your first table with
nano particles, you will see that it is the same,
then what happened, the last column is
youth, and in the last two days,
all the PMs became presidents, hi re member, you
can also memorize your portable by rote, I like to lip lock, what is the
connection between the first and the tablet, don't
you, and but both have become ends and the
complete PM has become pain difference
accused, see how to do it, I will
tell you Dixit and red ball, so
which of those wounds will be underlined, that will also work,
red will also work, rate, my good child,
my good daughter, both work, mine also works, it is a
good option, similarly this, this
red ball will be quarter line, what else will you
see  How to download our normal old solar table, the
mail of nominative, I am red, you will also underline it,
what will happen for red, what
is the ball, nominative mail, look, I have
shared the rotator, that is why sad ist
ain rotator ball is simple, like Amazing
according to this, you have got that red ball's
doctor line from your old table, you had a
line in castes and here you will definitely get
road 0, yes, he is in the rot ball, similarly
if you want to download I play with red
ball and below it will be underlined, tubewell did it on the
heena name, a little change here,
see here if you see,
what is my tune, the end will be in the table of road, that is why
that plummet in routine, a little
change, if you see, then
basically what you have to do is first
add your thing for cutting, my simple,
now we will not try doing 12 and a half
because it will become very big and now
what I am going to do is below this
in the comment section below this video,
you check, if
you can do it then it is complete  If it
goes then you can check it and if someone
asks me then it is clear till here and so
mother ghee I will show you one by one
how we did it, we replaced that time and
whatever is made and replaced it, so
how will it happen in this also, for Play Store there will be
Microsoft and after
Tiny then my name will be Ishq Limit -
Protein, very simple but at least you are
Great Wall Ishq Limit, right thick ball,
next this Great Wall Speed ​​Limit, join
protein ball, completely electronic, right here,
if you have more then mother your his, if you have got
supplement free player, if it has reached here then
you are almost done, the
morning intake is going to be used very less, but
still we learn that, so
what have you seen till now, and the red ball will come, and the red
ball, now let us see
what happens for two Red Bulls, that communication happens, so
look at the table for that, it is a little different,
next day as I said you
can remember in your own way, it is easy to remember to keep it in the floor,
so what I saw,
what is the difference in the second table tennis table  The
last two call girls that are everyday are
not this, the last column is not this, only everything else has been done,
except for mine, my settings are
not eligible, understand in this table I
also confirmed the nominal Sara that there is only
one cup of Suzy two million and everything else was that
in the last table, like Agney, you have to remember that
you can decide on your own,
so let's try this too,
for mine, the bad girlfriend you
receive the Great Wall, this will be the counter line,
this measurement minute email, what will be the delay
and boil, also look here,
what is the nominal mail, that is the digest Detroit ball,
right now, why is it like this, there is no vision of every
language cup,
why did I put it here, but the nut address is the table, so
add this drop box, there the red
ball again, the counter liner positive mail,
your two that in the normal table, and here the
top ten alien is a little easy, the total will not be
this, yes Ben Rhodes in the oval and dad
I play with the red ball again, Southern
Channel and don't email dam here also
Below the Wonderland tubewell is an is killer with them broken in the
picture at so
it will take practice if you look at these theory but it will take
practice if you
see then you will be seeing three tables
because if there is nothing then there is one more table so
one table will be pretty mathematical in Rafi date
now the question is
how will it be fast so
for this I will give you a trick so
understand them calmly if you have
understood that these are three tables and
when to use them then next understand
that any language has four parts
chin in date and le combination reliance question in exam
means listening, reading, speaking and writing so there is
no tension in listening and reading that you saw that protable friend get up Anmol show me
Red Bull then this is not really
wary about them then what is the separation and Shraddha
in Shraddha Paksha still you have
time whenever there is such a situation that time is
called during that so that's why
I  I will think about this table, you have
time to think, you can think and then
you can write this answer and the plan is to
speak about special things here and there and this camp, you will
see three tables and see the answer, so
I have a way for this, friends, here I
use a little from my side, there is a one level, cool job without
article table,
use that tight every time, it has two benefits, one is that it is
like the pain of the pain, so if you have a
split automatic hair, then this kilometer
temple will come automatically, it is very
intuitive and secondly,
if you do it in many places anyway, then a math's per
cent of the time has happened and in both of these
pieces also ok by and
against that much you will get a course in accuracy, you should
find it directly, it is very important that you do
these three tables, so the trick that
I told you is that in the beginning, without
thinking first, try to use as much of the practical table directly,
as time goes by
The more you do it, the more you will
remember yourself. Speed
limit means protein. I just did it for
5, 6, 7, so I remember this
and that. You will also remember this. Don't worry about it, it will come
with time. The
goal in the beginning is at least
90% accuracy in speaking.
Anyway, Sharma and I have enough
time in writing. It does
n't make any difference to animals, and
more than that, it doesn't make any difference to us.
Okay, so before concluding, if you forget what I am going to say in the next 2 minutes as soon as
you hear it, it's okay,
but just to our
conservative, we will see the adjective inside. Firstly, how many will we
use countless,
how many will we use attractive in it, and it will be used in
different parts. Purchase to complete the concept.
I give you a sentence.
Who says I like my old car's color, but bring it to
life in old car's color, so what will happen,
see what is this mask power, something for,
meaning colors of female, so what is that here,
Apun Jagdish, on this  I killed it but now
what will happen after that what is my car micra car
what is nominated government but
in this case that additive because - and toll on that
if you see what is in inactive
additive and some see the work of neutral is the same that is why in
this Madhuri 5th - alone in autos don't give
example if you want to do this then
I have told you how to do it it is
not normal so let us come back to our basics what
we do everything so what does that
mean in the beginning as you
saw well baby girl well that is
why in my baby my baby it may take
time - it may take time it was good well it had become
next
level problems that
Ajay table was not three tables and for jaggery
if there is a separate race for A and
only for jaggery then we calmly did
one table after another see I have
a floor to see that first I get it done without party
and after that I go to and
after that if you want to remember it like this then
you can remember it separately  Yes, the
trick I said is that whoever I am,
if you have come and have a car, then you have come and have come,
now if you have a car, then don't like, if you have come
and do it, then don't like and
look at the respectful table, this is very very simple, you have to
remember it in laser York, it does
not matter to them, we have enough time in this ribbon, we
can do it by writing Equitable somewhere, if you want to do it, do
not take tension in the operation and
directly, whatever is without article, that is
intuitive, just press this button, say the
roti ball directory of speed limit, a little bit of
electrician, that much we
can take in this test, the photo of you speaking in the council is
more important, to
get it absolutely hundred percent decorative, so guys,
this is dust and make no mistake, this is the
concept, brothers,
I have learnt it for six-seven years, still editors
and always come right for new all songs, so it will take
time, it will come only with practice
and how is it that a little bit like your
grandmothers, like ours, they
So I had never learnt Hindi from mouth like this but
he writes the character of the character very precisely so similar to correctly than
how much without learning Hindi grammar, just like the
more you use it,
it will become easy but until you do not know it, if you
do it step by step then there will be
no mistake, it has become slow but there is
no mistake, as you
go ahead your mind will get wasted
and then you will be able to forget it directly,
I hope you have understood this cancer,
we will meet in the next episode,
thank you.